usaultimate.org 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY**

USA Ultimate is a general audience website. As an interactive website, we collect certain personal information, which is more fully outlined below.

While we encourage children to engage in our interactive website, we also wish to educate parents and kids about issues of privacy when visiting our site.

As a result, we are committed to full compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"). We collect from children only that information which is necessary for participation. In addition, we have provided parents with the ability to review the type of personal information currently collected about their children, to have that information deleted, and to request that no further personal information be collected by USA Ultimate.

USA Ultimate respects and protects the privacy of our users. We encourage parents and kids to use and enjoy our Web site. Our privacy policy as described below is spelled out with the intention of educating parents and kids about how to safeguard their privacy when surfing on the web. We urge parents to discuss with their children the importance of protecting the confidentiality of personally identifiable information.

**  
WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED AND HOW WE COLLECT IT**

To enable visitors to participate in some of our online activities, we may ask them to provide personal information including name, e-mail address, telephone number and date of birth. Here are some of the ways we collect personally identifying information from our visitors:

• account creation  
• contest registrations  
• online surveys  
• online purchasing  
• forums registration

**  
HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION**

This information may be used for internal marketing purposes and helps us determine how to continually improve our site. We do not sell, distribute, trade or otherwise transfer personally identifiable information obtained from a user to any third party, either within our own organization or outside it, unless the user has provided his or her consent. We never share children's personal information with third parties.

Members may receive emails from USA Ultimate with program updates as well as offers/benefits on behalf of our partners. Individuals may unsubscribe from receiving these emails. We do not provide email address lists directly to sponsors or other third parties.

**  
THIRD-PARTY SITES AND SPONSORS**

Our site contains links to other sites whose information practices may be different from ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices, which may differ from ours.

**  
COOKIES AND HOW WE USE THEM**

Cookies are used to gather basic tracking information and to monitor the presentation of advertisements and are placed on your hard drive by many major websites. They are especially necessary when ordering a product online. Cookies allow websites to determine the type of computer operating system and browser that you and other viewers are using, which enables websites to improve access to content.

We do not link the information collected through cookies to personally identifiable information provided by users from participating in our activities. Cookies do not contain any information that is, in itself, personally identifying.

**  
TERMS OF USE**

Unless otherwise noted, all "Content" found on this website, including, but not limited to, photographs, graphics, editorial content, results, database information and any other text is the sole property of USA Ultimate or its partners, and all rights are reserved. The logos appearing on the Site which identify USA Ultimate and/or its products and services are proprietary marks.  The Content of this website is for your personal or informational use only.

Commercial usage of any content or the re-purpose of such content is strictly prohibited.  

For permission to use content with appropriate credit and in an editorial, non-commercial fashion, please contact USA Ultimate.

**  
QUESTIONS?**

Contact [webmaster@usaultimate.org](mailto:webmaster@usaultimate.org) for more information.
